bug.
Translation, Timing, Subs: @bugkkura. Huge thanks to @IAmOnlyWhoIAm for QC-ing! 🖤
(Sakura's mic was off for the first minute.)
I've completed a task. Now...
Is there any sound?
Can you hear me?
Can you hear me well? Is it too soft? Is it not too soft?
Too loud?
Hold on, everyone.
The sound is not soft?
Hold on.
As far as I know, this is really difficult. Seriously.
It's really difficult.
Wait, hold on everyone. Thank you.
How's the sound?
Too loud? Can you hear well?
Hold on. (Unintelligible)
The in-game sound is too loud...
The in-game sound is too loud, right?
Settings...
I don't know!
I really don't know what to do!
Can you let me try hearing myself first?
Let me try hearing my voice first. I'm turning this off for a second.
Uhm...
How's this? How is it?
Is it all right?
Is this okay?
How is this?
What about now?
How is it now, everyone?
It's okay? Then I'll get started.
First off...
It has started!
Let me move over.
I'm finally starting.
It's so-
This is my first time doing a live stream.
Also, this time I'm streaming from my PC instead from my laptop...
So I was extremely nervous.
Even though I started setting up at 6pm, I'm still late. I'm sorry, everyone.
So!
So, so, so. With that...
I will be streaming PlayStation 4's Amazing Spider-Man.
Yay~~~~! Omg.
Omg.
Oh, that was a bit noisy.
Because this is a headset, my breathing might be a bit noisy.
All right! So...if you see this up here, you'll know.
I've played a bit already.
A little.
So I'll...
...delete it.
Bye bye, data!
I've recorded a video of my gameplay once but..
If it isn't a livestream then I'm not able to film a Spider-man video.
So this time...
I decided to livestream my Spider-man gameplay.
I'm sure some of you are seeing this for the first time
but I want to let you know how great this game is.
This game is amazing!
A godly game.
How do I lower the in-game sound?
Hold on- (can't hear)
Game...
This seems to work.
Live stream...
Because this is my first time doing this so...
Please understand, everyone.
It's incredibly...
It's not working...
Let me turn this off for a bit.
How is this?
Whatever! Let's go.
Start!
Let's play, let's play.
Wow this spiderman is really..the difficulty is really high.
I've tried to play Amazing Spider-Man before and
even the tutorial took me one hour to complete.
This time, I want to make it a bit easier.
I don't want you guys to watch me struggle.
So the difficulty level I'll be playing is 'Friendly'.
What's that?
Please teach me how to adjust the in-game volume, everyone.
Or I guess I will to speak louder then everyone lower your volumes.
It should be okay as long as I can hear my own voice...
Oh, whatever.
This is my first time so-
please watch over me gently-
Oh~ It's like a movie!
If the in-game sound is too loud,
just treat it as if you're watching a movie.
It's really like a movie.
Oh, the sound from the PC.
I've lowered the volume.
Isn't this awesome?!
It's crazy. It's just like a movie.
So cool!
Games nowadays are really amazing.
Police Dispatch: All units, level four mobilisation. Location-- Fisk Tower.
Spider-Man: Fisk?
Spider-Man!
He's Spider-Man.
(???)
Oh, right. Did you know that Spider-Man shoots
spiderwebs from his bracelet?
I thought he shoots the spiderwebs from his wrists but
He actually shoots his spiderwebs from his bracelets.
The spiderwebs are from the device.
I didn't know before...
Police Dispatch: SWAT is 10-84 at Fisk Tower. All units standby, warrant is en route.
Whoa~ It's starting, everyone!
Whoa!!! He's flying.
No, no, I'm not doing anything yet.
I'm going now!
I'm doing this! I'm doing this!
I'm doing this, FYI!
Isn't this amazing?!!
This is awesome!!!
Yuri Watanabe: Captain Watanabe.
Spider-Man: Did you take him down yet?
Yuri Watanabe: No.
Yuri Watanabe: We're at Fisk Tower, but still waiting on the warrant.
Spider-Man: Mind if I join in on the fun?
Yuri Watanabe: You know how his lawyers are...this one needs to go by the book.
Spider-Man: C'mon Yuri, I've been waiting eight years for this.
Yuri Watanabe: You really want to help?
Yuri Watanabe: Head to Times Square, sounds like his guys
are trying to keep my backup from reaching the scene...
Spider-Man: You got it - almost there!
Ahhh oh no!
Hitting the building like that...that must've really hurt.
Isn't this aweeeeeeeeeeee~someeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee?!!!!!!!!!
This!
Spider-Man: Hello?
Boss: Parker?
Boss: Where are you?
Boss: We must run through the demonstration
at least once before the grant committee arrives.
I'm going!
Spider-Man: Uhh, yes. Sorry. Yes. Dealing with a...
personal issue. I'll be in soon. Promise.
See, Spider-Man also says so.
Spider-Man: Eesh, better wrap this up quick, then get to my *real* job.
It's a little funny now.
Isn't this so great??! Seriously!
Ouch.
This is really high.
Spider-Man: Looks like Yuri called in the cavalry.
This is amazing~
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here!
Here it comes, here it comes.
I'm so nervous!
It's those people.
Police Officer: We need more backup!
Police Officer: 10-32, Times Square. Officers under fire!
Now, now, now. Everyone, calm down. Because Spider-Man is on the way.
Fisk Thug: Bring in the hammer.
Miyawaki-
Miyawaki Spider-Man is coming. Don't worry, everyone.
Police Officer: *MOVE!*
That's so bad. They're really a bunch of bad people.
Where's Spider-Man? Has he not arrived yet?
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
He's here, he's here!!
Fisk Thug: Get him!
It's me!
Spider-Man: Morning guys! Who's ready for their hot fresh cup of bodily harm?
Fisk Thug: The boss sends his regards.
How do I do this?
Spider-Man: Gotta warn you, I'm feeling punchy today.
Hold on, hold on, hold it. I forgot how to do this.
Spider-Man: Next customer!
Spider-Man: This is bad.
All right, all right.
What's next?
Fisk Thug: Somebody just shoot him!
Spider-Man: Man, Fisk has a lot of guys on his payroll...
Isn't he really cool? Spider-Man!
Yuri Watanabe: Spider-Man, what's your status?
Spider-Man: Almost done here. You?
Yuri Watanabe: We're about to go in.
Spider-Man: Be there soon
Spider-Man: Can't wait to see Willie's face when you slap the cuffs on him.
This is amazing. (???)
(???)
It's done!
He's so strong! Since I'm playing the easiest mode.
Spider-Man: Okay, Yuri, all done. What's happen--
All right~
Spider-Man: Yuri?
Spider-Man: Yuri!
This is easy! (?)
Whoa~ Times Squaaareeeeeeee!!!
Spider-Man: I knew Fisk wouldn't go quietly.
I've only been to Times Square once.
Oh, right.
You know, seriously...When I was standing right at the
famous Times Square...I thought, "This is the world!"
(Unintelligible)
Here it comes! Everyone!
Ah, I'm nervous. Despite being Spider-Man...
Yuri Watanabe: Get more backup!
And lock down the airspace--
Spider-Man: Yuri, you okay?
Yuri Watanabe: If he makes it out of the building we're gonna lose him.
T/N: The translated gameplay dialogue is from the English version so it is a little different from the dialogue in the Japanese version. Sakura repeated the dialogue from the Japanese version.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Spider-Man: I'm gonna go, uh...
Go, go, go, go!
Yuri Watanabe: Do your thing.
Spider-Man: Yes!
I'm such a loser, aren't I?
Spider-Man: Today's the day, Willie.
Since this is the lowest difficulty.
Do I seem pathetic since this is easy mode?
Spider-Man is so cool!
Spider-Man: Hey, where you going?
Isn't he basically barehanded?
Spider-Man: Catch!
Let's go, go, go, go!
Spider-Man: I'll clear a path, follow me!
Police Officer: Get outta here, Spider-Man, we got this!
Oh no.
Spider-Man: Sorry to break it to you, but you do NOT got this, buddy.
Police Officer: What's Spider-Man doing here-- he's gonna mess everything up!
Spider-Man: Thanks for the confidence boost, guys!
Nice, nice, nice!
Next. What's next?
Where's the next one?
Bam, bam, bam, bam!
All right, next!
Spider-Man: I guess this is what they call a hostile workplace.
Look at this! Look at this!
Aren't I strong? There's nothing here.
Look! Isn't this great?
Oh no.
Gotta be quick.
Gotta be fast!
Faster!
More enemies are appearing.
All right, next!
Next! Nice! Great!
Who's next?
Huh? What's this?
They're coming!
Police Officer: Down, down, down!
Spider-Man: Gotta take those shooters out.
Hurry! Hurry!
Someone's there.
Spider-Man: I think that's all of 'em!
So. Strong.
Police Officer: C'mon, c'mon!
I did all of those moves just now.
Police Officer: They shut the elevators down! Take the stairs!
Because this is easy mode.
Spider-Man: I prefer a more direct approach.
But this is a lot of fun, really.
This game has a very exhilarating feeling.
There's something there- oh no!
Yuri Watanabe: Spider-Man, status?
Spider-Man: Heading to the upper floors--
and hoping nobody turns on the elevators...
What's going on?
Yuri Watanabe: Our choppers are taking fire,
looks like Fisk has armed men on every floor.
Spider-Man: He's desperate...
Yuri Watanabe: ...and he's hitting us with everything he's got.
Spider-Man: I have to find him and end this.
I'm entering~
Yuri Watanabe: Not yet.
Yuri Watanabe: We just picked up chatter -
they're wiping all their data servers.
Yuri Watanabe: We need that evidence if we want to put him away for good.
Data server...
Spider-Man: Okay, server room it is.
How do I...
Spider-Man: Call from May. Better answer.
Spider-Man: Uh...hi Aunt May.
Aunt May: What is all that noise?
Spider-Man: Watching a Super Hero movie. What's up?
Let's go!!
Aunt May: I just wanted to make sure we were still on for dinner tomorrow night.
Ah ah- that hurts!
Spider-Man: Totally. Uh, listen, I gotta go--
Aunt May: Okay, love you.
Spider-Man: Love you too.
Oh no!
Their guns are strong!
Where did they go?
Isn't he so strong?
There's more?!
Spider-Man: How exactly do you think this ends well for you?
There's so many of them!
Luckily they don't have guns.
Ah, that hurts!
Cool!
Not bad. Oh that-
Ouch! That hit really hurt!
It's all right if they don't have a gun.
It's done?
Spider-Man: Gotta find that server room before there's no evidence left.
Server room?
Is it there?
Spider-Man: If I go in this way, they'll destroy all the evidence.
R3.
Spider-Man: I should look for a sneaky way in.
It's here.
Spider-Man: There we go.
Spider-Man: It's like my own private ventrance.
Nice~
Spider-Man: Fisk may be a dirty criminal,
but he has remarkably clean air vents.
Fisk Thug: Hurry up! The boss wants everything erased!
Fisk Thug: I can't make it delete any faster.
Spider-Man: They're so cute when they're oblivious.
Isn't this extremely scary?
Fisk Thug: How's it coming?
Fisk Thug: Halfway there. Just need another minute or two.
Fisk Thug: You think the cops know where we are?
Fisk Thug: Don't worry about out there. Worry about in here.
Ah, I'm so nervous!
Let's go, everyone!
Spider-Man: Is this tech support? I forgot my password.
Fisk Thug: Spider-Man!
Fisk Thug: Don't let him near the console!
Ouch.
Automated Voice: Warning. Full deletion imminent.
Spider-Man: And I thought the IT guys at my last job were rude.
I can't dodge!
Ouch!
I'm going to die!
Nice.
There's one more.
Spider-Man: Gotta access that console before everything's gone.
Spider-Man: Let's see just how good their security is.
Spider-Man: Oh you guys forgot the latest kernel patch, tsk-tsk...
Wilson Fisk: Hiding in the server room?
I can't read your comments...
Wilson Fisk: Cowardly...even for you.
I'm doing well, right!
Spider-Man: Says the guy frantically erasing his search history.
I haven't died once yet, until now. Since it's easy mode.
Wilson Fisk: After all these years, you're still just an ignorant child...
He's a bad...bad guy.
Spider-Man: True, but that's part of my charm, isn't it?
Is Fisk a character that appears in the movie? I...
Wilson Fisk: Damn you.
... only watched Spider-Man 1 before.
T/N: The first movie.
Wilson Fisk: Get that door down, now!
Wilson Fisk: Get past him. Destroy everything!
Wilson Fisk: Look around you! I did this!
Wilson Fisk: What have you ever done that mattered?
Spider-Man: Well, there was that time I took down a pompous,
overstuffed crime lord before breakfast.
Wilson Fisk: Without me, the scum I kept in check will
run rampant.
Wilson Fisk: And it'll be all your fault.
Spider-Man: Been a long, tough road, Fisk. Almost sad to see it end.
Eugh, more of them entered. Somehow.
Wilson Fisk: Mere prelude.
Ouch!
Spider-Man: Well, get ready for the main event.
Okay, nice.
Oh no~
I really want to recover my health.
Spider-Man: Yuri, an explosion just--
This is bad, this is bad, this is bad.
Yuri Watanabe: I saw it.
Yuri Watanabe: Fisk could have the whole place wired. I'm sending in a bomb unit.
Tutorial...
Oh, they're here.
Spider-Man: I'll make sure no one gets in their way.
Gun! They have guns again.
The one with the gun- this is dangerous.
Coo- Awesome!
Spider-Man: I think that's all of 'em.
Okay.
Done.
Police Officer: It's clear, move up!
Nice~
Spider-Man: Hey guys--
Spider-Man: I guess bombs are part of Willie's getaway plan.
Spider-Man is so cool~
Spider-Man: Sounds like they're trapped...
Bomb Squad Officer: You go after them, we'll look for the bombs--
Isn't this pretty smooth?
It's really warm...
There!
Spider-Man: Everyone clear out!
Run, run!
Spider-Man: Evacuate the building!
Is that an enemy? I can't tell if they're a friend or an enemy.
Okay.
Woman: I heard more people back that way!
Got it.
Spider-Man: I'll find them.
Woman: Spider-Man! We can't move, we're pinned down!
There!
Be careful!
Spider-Man: I'll lift it. When you're free, get out, fast.
If you can walk, help the injured. Got it?
Use strength!
Everyone, please cheer for Spider-Man.
Say, "go Spider-Man!"
Ahhhhh please!
Spider-Man: Go, go, go!
Woman: Thank you!
That's so cool.
Woman: He did it! Let's go!
Spider-Man: Okay Willie, comin' your way.
Spider-Man's a regular person, right?
Yuri Watanabe: Spider-Man, it's Yuri.
I think he was before...
Spider-Man: How we doing, Captain?
Yuri Watanabe: Could be better. Our choppers took
a beating-- we just had to ground our last one.
Yuri Watanabe: If Fisk calls in a chopper,
we have no one to stop it from landing.
Spider-Man: And no one to chase him if he flies away...
Yuri Watanabe: Why do I get the feeling that's what he was planning all along?
Spider-Man: Because he probably was.
Spider-Man is a regular person...
How should I put it...
Ordinary people...
Spider-Man: Damn.
Spider-Man: Yuri, get EMTs up here-- fast!
Ordinary people won't be able to do things like this. Definitely not.
Yuri Watanabe: We're trying--
He definitely got some powers from the somewhere before.
Stuntman.
Spider-Man: Uh-oh-- INCOMING!
RUN!!!
Rockets are unfair. This isn't even Fortnite...
Spider-Man: That's enough out of you...
Spider-Man: More rockets? Little excessive don't you think?
Spider-Man: What--? Is it national rocket day or something?
Oh no!
Can't it be opened normally...
Spider-Man: Man, how'd the bomb squad guys get through this?
Oh? I can go there.
Fisk Thug: He's here! Get 'im!
Spider-Man: Settle down, I've got enough for everybody.
Oh no, oh no.
Only the guns! Only the guns! Only the one with the guns! Oh no!
Take down those with guns first.
Is he the one with the gun?
Spider-Man: Okay, room is clear.
Spider-Man: Bomb squad must be somewhere ahead--
Spider-Man: hope they're okay.
Careful...
Oh it can be opened.
The difference between opening the door normally and destroying it.
Spider-Man: You guys all right?
Bomb Squad Officer: We were just about to call for backup.
Spider-Man: I think I'm it.
Bomb Squad Officer: Lead the way, we'll be right behind you.
Got it.
Bomb Squad Officer: Heads up, boss...
I'm here, aren't I?
Watch out!!
Right, he's Spider-Man.
Spider-Man's reaction is really fast.
Spider-Man: You guys were in bed with Fisk all along?
Aww now I'll never get that image out of my head!
What, eh? Wait, wait, wait.
This guy with the gun is annoying.
Spider-Man: So your plan didn't work.
Spider-Man: On to plan B-- getting kicked in the face.
(Unintelligible)
Gun gun gun! The guy with the gun! The guy with the gun!
They're extremely dangerous.
Those with guns are the most dangerous.
Finish this first- Someone's there!
Thaaat reaaally huuurt!! Seriously!!
What was that?!!
Spider-Man: Hey Yuri, looks like some of
your guys were on Fisk's payroll.
Spider-Man: Good news is, they were Willie's last line of defense.
I'm right outside his office.
Those with guns are too much. I'm using my bare
hands so everyone should fight bare-handed!
Yuri Watanabe: Take him down. Now.
Spider-Man: With pleasure.
It's unfair.
Boss boss boss boss.
Last boss, last boss.
Last boss?
Spider-Man: Writing your memoirs?
It's extremely warm in here.
Spider-Man: Don't forget the hyphen between "Spider" and "Man."
Spider. Man.
Wilson Fisk: Get the chopper ready.
Wilson Fisk: I won't be long.
Does everyone know that there's a hyphen between "Spider" and "Man"?
I only found out recently.
Wilson Fisk: I'm surprised you made it this far.
Wilson Fisk: But your foolishness ends now.
Up until now, I haven't died once.
That's sly.
Spider-Man: Uh...you do know I can still see you, right?
Wilson Fisk: Eight years of this insolence...
Oh no!
Spider-Man: For me? You shouldn't have...
Spider-Man: Gotta wait for an opening.
This is hard!!
Spider-Man: It's reloading.
Is it R1 or R2? No idea.
Oh no!!
R1. R1, R1. It's R1.
Ah, R. R.
Wait, wait, wait.
Ah!! Wait, wait, wait.
Calm down for a moment.
Huh?
Wilson Fisk: What are you doing?
Ahhh that was dangerous.
I thought I was going to die.
That was scary.
That was dangerous.
Wilson Fisk: How is this happening?!
Spider-Man: What's wrong, Willie? You seem angry...
For your information, this is a tutorial.
Isn't this too much? It's so hard.
Wilson Fisk: I will DESTROY you!
Eh, 25??
T/N: Sakura is referring to her HP.
No recovery??
Spider-Man: Take your best shot!
I want to recover.
Hold on!
Wait!!
He's too strong!! I can't recover. I need to recover.
I need a potion!
Wait wait wait! I only have 1 HP left-
This guy- STAY BACK!! This is hard.
Oh god!
Oh no, oh no, oh no. This is very bad.
I can only dodge now!
1 HP?! Isn't 1 HP too dangerous?
No but...isn't it too hard with only 1 HP left?
Recover...you can't recover whenever you want to.
Again, again.
Seriously-
He's so strong!
That-- hurts!
His one hit is too strong!
Almost done.
He keeps talking!
Not bad, right?
Take this-
Oh! Huh?
The story-
All right~
Don't!
He's so strong!
Only Spider-Man can take his beatings.
Wilson Fisk: You are everything that's wrong with this city!
Isn't it amazing that he's an equal match to
Spider-Man when he's fighting bare-handed?
Spider-Man: Huh...I was gonna say the same to you.
Wilson Fisk: You know what to do, men.
Fisk Thug: Surround him!
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no.
Get rid of the thugs first!
All right~
Ouch!
I kicked air.
That was dangerous!
That was painful!!
OH NO!!
Dodge, dodge. Calm down, calm down, calm down first.
There's nothing else.
WAIT!!
STOP!!!
Too strong!!
Retreat, retreat, retreat.
Fisk...is so strong.
First.
Get rid of the one holding a gun.
WHOA!!!
That's a bit too strong.
You're not holding a gun- wait, wait.
That hurts!
Hey, hold on.
One- Come one by one!
Come one at a time!
What, what, what??
Let me calm down for a second.
First...
I need to relax.
Relax and take them one by one...
But really, he's too strong.
Maybe it becomes harder when they're all grouped together.
All right.
I have to dodge!
I'm dodging!
Dodging is important.
Good, good, good.
Why?!
Hold it, hold it.
Tie him up.
After tying him, get back.
Then regenerate webs.
Tie him again.
Retreat again!
Oh no!
Tie him one more time!
When he's tied-
All right! Got him. Okay.
Then get away! Immediately.
Then, tie him.
What, did I get hit?
Whyyy do you receive damageee from fireeee?????
Speaking of, I haven't tried recovering my HP once.
Ouch.
I think today's livestream will end after the tutorial.
How much HP can you recover with HP recovery?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh no!!
Save me, everyone!
Hold on, get rid of this guy first. He's really strong.
Oh no, oh no, this guy is too strong! Overwhelmingly.
Good. This is the only way to fight him.
Careful not to get too close to fire.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
I can only fight this way.
Bit by bit.
Oh no.
This is the only thing I can do!
Oh!!
We're going into the story, everyone!
Watch out!!
Come on, Spider-Man!
It's a movie.
There it is, there it is.
Spider-Man's victory!!
Spider-Man: So, should we kiss now?
Spider-Man: Maybe later.
It's warm.
Got it. You can't overdo it. I got it now.
Oohhhhh.