Translation, Timing: @bugkkura
QC: @IAmOnlyWhoIAm
Everyone, long time no see.. I'm Miyawaki Sakura.
It has really been a long time, but I updated my YouTube channel after a long while.
An Update After 1 year!!
What game will I be playing this time?
It is a game called "Little Nightmares II".
Why I'll be playing the second one first...
Even though Little Nightmares II was only just released recently
But it's one of the games that I've been wanting to play for a long time.
But the first one...I've seen the entire story from watching other gamers' gameplay videos.
So..
Even though I feel like everyone might not understand this game, so I should start from 1...
I don't care. I want to play 2 so I'm going to start from 2.
Gonna do it my way
Strong-willed
This year's Sakura seems different
So while...watching me play Little Nightmares, if you think, "Oh! This looks fun!"
You can play 1 first before watching this video, or you could watch other people's gaming videos then come here.
Anyhow! After watching gameplay videos of Little Nightmares 1, I thought it was really fun.
I wanted to play it myself but even just watching others' live gameplay was already so captivating.
So this time, I will challenge Little Nightmares 2.
I'll do my best... until the end... Let's go!
Whether I can clear the game...
Please don't expect anything (；∀；)
From here on, the mic is too near so the sound might sometimes crackle, please do note
Well, let's start at once.
Speaking of, this is my first time using this remote control.
Why is it B to the right and A to the bottom?
Don't complain
from the start (cry)
It's super hard to use, I want to change it.
I'm nervous! Eh but this game is quite scary. Although it isn't exactly a horror game.
It also has puzzle-solving elements, so I'm uneasy on whether I can clear it.
(coughs)
Oh it's already scary.
What kind of story will it be...
Since it's a game that needs to be explored, there should be a proper story.
Ah! That scared me!
It's going to be noisier, please take note
That REALLY scared me. The remote control is vibrating!!
Sca~ry. I was scared to death.
The viewers are probably
more frightened by my breathing
I'm sorry (cry)
The graphics are great.
Which is to dash?
Dash is this.
Dash is this. What about jump? Eh?
This being can actually talk.
Holding.
Jump, jump is A. What about B?
I'm not sure yet.
Run and then...
The graphics are BEAUTIFUL!
My breathing is too noisy (cry)
I have to go here, I guess.
Whoa, this is scary. Speaking of, can I adjust the vibration?
It really scared me just now.
Seems like I can walk up here?
Hey~
HEY~
This is so cute! I didn't know it can speak.
Hey~
Wow~
What is this?
Basically, there's a lot of bugs...
Jump. Okay~ Oh that was close.
Ya this - the in-game world was designed amazingly.
Ah, it's here. Should be easy.
Wait...
How do I open it?
Press RT and push on L
While pressing RT-
Ah, I see, got it.
RT is for grabbing, right?
I can't squat down!
LT for squat
Ah, they tell you everything.
Thank you~
So gentle
Wow the graphics are really amazing! I have to squat here.
I have to squat while walking to get out from here.
This is amazing!
Is it because of the music? It's extremely thrilling.
I'm really sorry, the sound might crackle because of the headphones.
Understood
Expressing my apologies again (cry)
I'm very sorry about that.
What's this?
Oh I can pick it up.
Eh?
Human bodies?
Shoes..are these their shoes?
Really creepy. Let's just leave quick.
Which button's jump?! Ah...
I can't do anything once I panic.
Jump! Jump- wait I can't jump up.
Jump! Eh?
Dash and jump!
Ah I'm stuck. I'm stuck. I'm stuck.
Eh wait wait, this is weird, this is weird.
This way?
No it isn't...
Press RT to hang
Press RT to hang.
Sorry, I need to be taught everything.
RT button- This computer... this is on a computer- This- (in Korean)
Ah... Korean slipped out.
It's my first time using this remote control so I'm not used to it.
Hang?
Huh?
Someone who gets angry
when it's clearly her problem
RT is this, right?
Got it, got it.
I got mad right away.
Scary, scary. I can drop down.
Jump!
That looked a little painful?
There should be no damage from falling, right? Is there?
Ah, there is..
This is definitely going to catch me.
Is there no way to choose where to go from here?
Can I walk around from here?
Guess not.
Ah if I jump over, I won't be caught, got it.
Jump!
That's definitely a place where you'll be trapped.
Amazing, it seems like a place where people will definitely be caught.
Ah the vibration is really annoying!
Ah, it's not here?
Doesn't look like it's here.
Ah it can be moved.
Oh not bad, I'm playing really well, aren't I?
Put it here, right?
Then, jump.
J-jump. After jumping.. I still don't really remember the instructions.
Hurry up and
remember the controls
Looking good.
Squat.
X to run
WAIT!! Where's X?? Ah, wait-
Everyone, please don't be frustrated yet (cry)
X to run
I can't remember - we usually use B to dash.
That's right - We often use B for dashing
Quickly quickly quickly.
It's so fast! Can I even make it?
That was scary...
This place...I definitely have to go up...
Can I take this?
Nope.
Looks like I have to swing from there...
But how do I get up there? Can I go up?
Do I bring this rock with me?
I can't take it.
Eh wait wait, how do I go - can someone teach me?
I can't climb up, right?
I'm stuck, teacher.
This- ah!
This game is amazing!
Jump!
Oh no, I'm stuck. I'm really stuck.
Eh? Ah... I didn't grab onto the rope just now.
Wait, until now I still haven't- B is to dash. This is seriously difficult.
Hurry up and remember (2nd time)
X is to run, A is to jump.
Jump and then grab it!
Swing back.
Yes! Okay.
Okay okay okay okay.
And then for this...
Let it down to the right height... Stop here...
Then jump on it, jump.
Okay okay okay okay okay okay okay.
This level is- but it's probably still the tutorial.
Let's run along.
How do I get across? Won't I just die?
There's some really eerie music playing in the background.
Do I pick this up? This rope.
My only option is to die-
Ah... there's a path below.
Owh! Looks painful.
Climb up from here.
Although it's hard, it's still extremely fun!
I love this type of game. Even though it's scary.
Go down here- ah!
Seriously can you not do that?!!
Ah..Seriously...The remote control's vibration is really too much.
I've been saying 'remote control' but it should be 'controller'
Shoes. I like the red shoes.
Seems like there's a lot of red shoes.
Wait this... is safe right?
Doesn't it look a lot like a trap?
Ack!! That scared me!!
Weren't you shocked by my voice?
I got it! I got it now.
I have to take the shoes, right?
So that's how- so that's why there are shoes here.
First, pick it up.
How do I throw it?
Throw!
Go up quickly!
This... You probably wouldn't know what to do unless you die once, right?
If you understand, you'll know. But for me, I have to die once to understand.
Die at First Attempt (Only Miyawaki) Game
Wait wait, these should be traps too?
They all look like traps!
They're all definitely traps! What do I do?
Ah I just have to be careful?
I guess so, it's just reminding me to be careful of these.
Jump and then...
This looks like something I have to take.
Ah I got it.
Take~ this. And then...
Bring it...thr-
Th-
Th~row! Alright.
Going well.
I can still handle this level. WOOO~ So fun.
This definitely has to be used.
I'm a little concerned about that wooden box- EUAH!! That scared me.
I was really scared by this place...seriously
Wait, this death- *SIGH*
That really scared me.
They all look suspicious, don't they?
Here! This one!
This!
I did it? Is there any more?
No idea so I'm just gonna jump over.
And there's tons of them - I can see them all.
I won't be caught by them again!
This is how you learn the game. I got it.
This is how you learn the game.
This place definitely has a bad vibe.
Isn't this place dangerous? I have to climb up, for sure...
Oh-
OOHWHOAAA!!
Nice.
Jump~ Okay.
Going well, going well.
Well I don't know if it's going great, it's still the tutorial, isn't it?
This is probably a game where you fall and learn.
It feels... There are so many small cages. It's so weird, really.
Look at the size of the house. It's clearly the size for normal human beings.
The darkness seems ill-boding...
So what exactly am I?
EYY!
I need to go in, for sure.
Ah, this is really bad.
Ah, really bad.
I'm going in.
I can't get up.
Ah, is that how?
Eh even though I definitely must go in...
I'm scared... I'm.. done for...
I'll open these for the time being- ah.
Sorry for being noisy.
Hold up, this... I want to open this, why did it close? I wanted to open it because I feel that's definitely something inside.
Ah I'm really sorry...
Looks like someone will enter, isn't it?
It's really really- it looks extremely frightening.
It's probably gonna be extremly scary- Speaking of what's scary...
This... remote control is vibrating. That is what's scary.
It's a controller
Is there anyone?
There's a music box.
Music box.
Where's the sound coming from?
Oh.
There's someone.
It's a friend......ly...right?
Right? Doesn't work.
Is it this?
Eeeeeeeeeeyap! Ah-
Alright...
I'll look here.
Ah the music is really scary. Is that it?
I can't grab it.
Oh it looks very heavy. Eeeyap! OHH I can definitely save you with this.
Is this person a child? I'm not sure if it's a boy.
Eh this is so amazing. Isn't this heavy?
So his posture when he walks is like this. His legs are visibly planting firm on the ground.
So his posture when he walks is like this.
His legs are visibly planting firm on the ground.
I like the attention to details
So his posture when he walks is like this.
His legs are visibly planting firm on the ground.
This makes me feel great to be born in this era, where games like this can be created.
The quality is too high. OH~
I'm here to save you.
Are you afraid?
I'm here to rescue you. It's all good now.
Sounds like a child - their voice. I'm here to save you.
I've come to save you.
I'm here for you.
Shy [towards strangers].
A child who's fearful of strangers.
Is there anything here? The child must've been locked in here and not been able to leave, right?
I feel like I can go up from here.
Don't die?! Ah, I got scared.
This is?
Is this the music box?
Ah I threw it- I didn't mean to do that.
Where are you going...
Don't run away?
I think it's better if I follow him.
Isn't it dangerous to go alone? This place definitely has someone dangerous.
Oh that scared me.
Quick quick quick.
Ah there's a scary music now.
There's definitely someone here.
Scared~me~to~death~
So noisy
What's this?
What's this? Are they alive? Real people? Dolls?
I got scared to death.
AHH I'm sorry!!
It's really hard to control the volume
I'm very sorry
You have to be quiet. The music is too scary, I can't.
Calm down. I have to calm down.
Can you reach it? You have to open that?
Do you need help? Got it, I'll help, I'll help.
I said I'll help. What? Why?
We have to go up, so I said I'll help. Got it, I got it.
Understood, understood.
Hold on a moment. We're a bit out of sync.
Rather incompatible
Don't change directions. Can I be lifted from any direction? Am I supposed to lift you? Ah...
It's a shoe.
Ah- We're exposed, we're exposed. We're definitely exposed!
We're definitely exposed! We have to hurry up.
I can't get up, I can't get up. Why can't I go up?
Hold on for a moment.
Please wait for a moment.
I can't go up, but I feel like I'm supposed to be able to..
Huge chaos
This is a bit weird.
I can't go up- Why did you open this? I can't climb up...
I can go up.
So that's how it is
I can go up now~
So scary. My stomach hurts, even though I don't actually have a stomach ache.
So what is it
It's a key.
I'm sure I have to take it. Wait, but I can't get over there.
Can't go from here. Are you following me?
You suddenly opened your heart to me.
How do I go over?
Wait, we're stuck here.
I'll lift you. I'll lift you like we did just now.
It's probably not here, right?
I'm stuck, I'm stuck.
I'm stuck. Can't you tell me what I should do? You should put in a bit of work too, help look around.
Can I go up here?
Here too...Is there anywhere to go through?
Not here.
This isn't it...
Ahh...
Push push, together.
Ahh~
Ahh~ Okay okay okay.
Looks like there's...
..a person, right?
It's a person that's inside right?
Looks like something must be inserted there, right?
How do I do this...From below?
Oh! You can do that for me?
I got it, but how do I jump.
Ah, okay okay okay.
I'll go get it.
Like this, right? "Go get it, you punk." Is it like that?
Don't say
"you punk" （；∀；）!!
Noticed something
That's definitely going to move, right?!?
Once I take it...she's definitely going to move...
Ex~cu~se~ me~
Excuse...
Me.
It's a doll.
Eh? What, what?
Take it- Okay okay okay okay.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Ah scary~ Scary~
I've got it~
Are you doing it?
That's nice of you.
Ah you'll turn- you'll turn it too. So nice.
I'll get it, I'll get it, I'll get it.
Is it hard?
It looks hard. Let's do it together.
Let's do it together.
Two incompatible people part 2
I want to do it with you but how does it work?
How are we supposed to do it together?
Do I hold onto you?
Ah...
Ah I fel- Oh~ OH~~
Go, go, go, go, go.
This is bad, this is bad.
Because~ weird music~ is starting to play~
If we don't leave quick...Here- together- Wait, let's do that again.
What? We're suddenly holding hands.
Can we hold hands?
Wait, why can't I go back?
Wait a moment...
Wait...What do I do?
From here?
Can't, can't.
But it's definitely this way. It's not it's not.
Ah. Pull this out.
Ah...
This is seriously~
Because my brain is not working that well.
I'm not used to this type of game.
But I was correct in guessing that it's definitely this way.
So you have to trust your gut, then think about your next step after.
Let's go~
But after inserting the key, it'll surely... Oh! It leads outside.
Is that all? Huh?
I thought I'll still be in the house.
Oh~ It's a large footprint.
I'll probably meet someone here, right?
I have a bad feeling...
Or maybe I'm the only one feeling this.
Do we move this?
Let's push together..that's the way.
It can only be pushed until here.
Then?
I can go from here?
Yup.
This...
An annoying sound...
This sound... Something bad is definitely going to happen.
It's a person. What should I do?
First time meeting a live human
I hope the teacher tells me...
If I don't go through...there is absolutely no place to hide behind.
I beg you, don't catch me~ please~
I just want to...
I just want, I just want to pass by...
Quick quick quick!!
RUN RUN RUN RUN!!
Run run run run run run
Where- WAIT WAIT WAIT WAIT WAIT WAIT WAIT WAIT
Suddenly respawned
I didn't get caught?
I got caught~
Run run!! I get it, I get it, I get it already!
Like this.
Then I can hide here.
Next, is here.
Quick quick quick quick.
Here right? I get it, I get it.
I get it now.
Then...
Is it here?
I'm gone, I'm gone, I'm gone!
I said I'm gone!
I'm not there, right? You don't know where we went.
There's nothing, right?
Told you!
Please please please.
Please, teachers... Oh no, we're doomed.
WHY ARE YOU- go-going-
Hide- why do you want me to come over?
Can we go now?
Why? This isn't the time to say "Please go first~".
Ah are you saying now is our chance [to escape]?
Hide, don't be exposed. Because we aren't exposed so we need to hide.
We aren't exposed so we need to slowly...AHHH!!!
We won't be exposed?
Look, there isn't anything, right?
It's all good.
We won't be exposed at all. Although I don't know why we aren't exposed.
Walk slowly and we won't be caught.
Please go first~
They're really not giving up.
Slowly, slowly.
Please~
Wait, we definitely have to run there, right? But...
Won't we die on the way there?
Though I know I won't be exposed here.
Ah, I got it, I got it. Go when they face that direction, right?
Wait a second...
Face that way. When he turns here, we can't be seen, right?
Why aren't we caught
Quick quick.
Wait, what about the other person? Oh, that's great.
He's coming, he's coming, he's coming.
He's coming, he's coming- AH!!
Ah...that scared me...
Alright.
Awesome.
I've temporarily escaped from danger.
The- The first- I think I've passed the first boss.
My fringe definitely
doesn't ever part this side
Do I pull this?
I've pretty much pulled it all the way, right?
Wait. Is he the type that will abandon me?
Sudden betrayal
Wait wait wait wait wait.
Suddenly abandoned?
Or was I supposed to run across first?
Wait, I suddenly got left behind...
I-
Y to call out
Ah.
Why was I suddenly left behind?
Well, it could happen, considering it hasn't even been 10 minutes since we met.
You go first.
Alright.
This is the first time I'm using shouting. There was a prompt just now.
Wait.
There, do something there.
Okay, okay.
I got- (in Korean) I got it, I got it.
Oh, are you just reaching out to help me?
Will that work? I'll trust you!
I trusted you!!
Go, I got it now. I just have to run a bit more, right?
Hey hey~
The voice sounds like a boy.
I'm going to run now.
Run and~~ Jump!
Okay~
Okay, okay~
Go, go.
Seems like there's something inside.
Do we have to save the child?
Does this game have it too?
There is a similar mission like saving a child in the first game.
Something like a subquest?
There was something like that.
But I can't rescue him~
I guess, I give up.
Not much can be done so I gave up early
This task is for those who can save him.
I have too much on my plate now.
Ah, that's not good.
Why are they still here?
Why are they still here? Why haven't they given up?
This is the worst!!
This is the worst!!!
I can't go up!!
Why does it feel like that kid keeps ditching me sometimes.
Whatever, forget it.
Eh?! I died like that? What happened?
Ah, I pressed the wrong button.
But there are times I feel at ease...
...because the child is here.
Quickly
I can't believe I was fine from that?
QUICKLY!! Pull me up please...
He should be giving up, right?
Or is he gonna do what he did just now...
This way, right?
This...
Why~ was~ I~ ex~po~sed~
Why?!!
After this, I died several times (cry)
So for this, I guess...
I need to hide all the way to be able to get across.
Why?
Alright.
What's that? A heart?
Why is there a heart on the tree?
It's alright, it's alright, it's alright.
You're doing better than expected. Great.
And then...
I know what to do here.
We're already here, please don't come this way again..seriously.
Don't, don't... Don't
Ya, I beg you!!!
But why, wait. It's weird.
Ah, I just have to go across quietly.
RUN QUICK!!
How do I run? It's X, right? I'm right!
I'll just run all the way straight.
At full speed.
Here.
Run run run run.
Run.
Okay okay okay okay.
Close, close. Close it all the way!
Is this the only thing I can do?
I have to get rid of him, will it be okay?
I even have goosebumps...is it okay to kill someone?
These kids seem okay after killing.
Then again the other guy is out to kill us so it's legitimate self-defense, right?
Does this mean the first part is over?
The first part. What's this?
Ah, together? Sorry.
This kid has been working hard lately.
Ah~ This is considered the first stage of escape, right?
I had so much cold sweat! I was shaking so hard!
Am I the only one who's scared?
Isn't it pretty scary?
To be honest everyone was probably scared
from my voice instead
But because...
I don't know if it's a boy or a girl - short hair-chan is here, I feel...abit more at ease.
Before, I was alone so it was quite scary.
Something's floating.
Using Mario as an example, I've finished the first stage, I think.
Once I reach the destination, I will wrap up this episode.
If the video is too long, it will be hard on the viewers...
It's already too long
So I'll end it here.
It's hot though- It's hot but I also feel cold.
Maybe it's because of the goosebumps but I feel hot yet cold.
Where does this go?
The scale of the game is amazing...
That's really huge.
For this game, even for the first game, there's no one telling the story nor there is a storyteller.
But when I played, the way how I still felt the underlying storyline, is really amazing.
Games that have their own world are amazing~
A game with a complete world is the best...
So fun.
We're here, we're here.
So today- eh you're not coming with me?
Being pushy (lol)
Heh.
Isn't it cute that they're holding hands?
Wait, because I discovered a new friend...
I'll greet him then wrap up.
Hey~
Hmm?
What happened?
Eh?
When this child appeared there was a TV set too...
Does the child have some bad memories related to a TV set?
Maybe some trauma...
Since the second stage will probably start once I enter...
Alright.
Miyawaki Sakura's Little Nightmares 2 part #1 will end here.
Thank you for watching!
See you in the next video!
Please look forward to #2! Bye bye~